(this.webpackJsonprr_trivia=this.webpackJsonprr_trivia||[]).push([[0],{44:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The song Police State by the political hip-hop group Dead Prez appeared on what landmark 2000 album?","correct":"Lets Get Free","answerA":"Lets Get Free","answerB":"RBG: Revolutionary but Gangsta","answerC":"Information Age","answerD":"Wake Up!"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The New Jersey based \\"Juice Crew\\" rapper Queen Latifah dropped this powerful song in 1993 pushing back against all of the disrespect aimed at women and girls in Hip-Hop. ","correct":"\\"U.N.I.T.Y.\\"","answerA":"\\"U.N.I.T.Y.\\"","answerB":"\\"Black Infinity\\"","answerC":"\\"You\'re a Black Women\\"","answerD":"\\"Who You Calling a Bitch?\\""},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS-  Eminem performed a scathing  freestyle rap attack against this politician and any of his fans who support him in October 2017. Who was the politician?","correct":"Donald Trump","answerA":"Donald Trump","answerB":"Hillary Clinton","answerC":"Joe Biden","answerD":"Barack Obama"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Killer Mike, political rapper and hip-hop activist based in Atlanta, Georgia endorsed which presidential candidate in 2016?","correct":"Bernie Sanders","answerA":"Bernie Sanders","answerB":"Michelle Obama","answerC":"Joe Biden","answerD":"Jill Stein"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This seminal hip- hop group\xa0was responsible for popularizing socially conscious hip-hop in the early 1980\'s with classics like \\"the Message\\" and \\"New York, New York.\\"","correct":"Grand Master Flash & the Furious 5","answerA":"Grand Master Flash & the Furious 5","answerB":"The Treacherous Three","answerC":"Run DMC","answerD":"The Sugar Hill Gang"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- J. Cole\'s \\"High for Hours,\\" released in early 2017, mentioned a meeting with which president?","correct":"Barack Obama","answerA":"Barack Obama","answerB":"Donald Trump","answerC":"George W Bush","answerD":"Bill Clinton"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This Oakland area based, radical hip-hop artist implored black people to \\"Break the Grip of Shame\\" in a 1990 hip-hip song. Who was the artist?","correct":"Paris","answerA":"Paris","answerB":"Mac Dre","answerC":"E-40","answerD":"Too Short"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This white, Seattle based, hip-hop artist wrote and performed the song \\"Same Love\\", which condemns homophobia in hip-hop.","correct":"Macklemore","answerA":"Macklemore","answerB":"Onry Ozzborn","answerC":"LL Cool J","answerD":"MC Search"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This neo hip-hop song off the Digable Planets 1993 debut album Reachin\' (A New Refutation of Time and Space) stands up for reproductive freedom for women.","correct":"\\"La Femme Fetal\\"","answerA":"\\"La Femme Fetal\\"","answerB":"\\"Where I\'m From\\"","answerC":"\\"Rebirth of Slick (Cool Like Dat)\\"","answerD":"\\"Nickel Bags\\""},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The UK rapper Slowthai released this album in 2019 with songs critical of Brexit and Theresa May.","correct":"Nothing Great About Britain","answerA":"Nothing Great About Britain","answerB":"This Ain\'t England","answerC":"I Wish I Knew","answerD":"God Made the Queen"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Which list of artists were all part of the political rap-rock \\"super group\\" Prophets of Rage? ","correct":"Jim Commerford, Tom Morello, Brad Wilk, DJ Lord, Chuck D, and B-Real","answerA":"Jim Commerford, Tom Morello, Brad Wilk, DJ Lord, Chuck D, and B-Real","answerB":"Brad Wilk, DJ Lord, Chuck D, B-Real and Snoop Dogg","answerC":"Tom Morello, Brad Wilk, DJ Lord, Chuck D, B-Real and Ice Cube","answerD":"Tim Commerford, Tom Morello, Brad Wilk, and Flea"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This rapper was visited by the Secret Service in 2018 in response to alleged threatening lyrics towards Donald Trump in his song  \\"The Ringer.\\" ","correct":"Eminem","answerA":"Eminem","answerB":"Snoop Dogg","answerC":"Tim Dog","answerD":"Ice Cube"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The hip hop artist Ice Cube pulled together and produced this LA\xa0based black nationalist\xa0rap group named after his record label.","correct":"Da Lynch Mob","answerA":"Da Lynch Mob","answerB":"WC and the Maad Circle","answerC":"EPMD","answerD":"Westside Connection"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The angry screed \\"Black Cop\\" by KRS-One appeared on what album? ","correct":"Return of the Boom Bap","answerA":"Return of the Boom Bap","answerB":"By All Means Necessary","answerC":"Criminal Minded","answerD":"I Got Next"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The East Bay radical political hip- hop artist Paris invited this New York based rapper on an extended mix track of the song \\"Field Nigga Boogie\\" off his 2003 album Sonic Jihad. ","correct":"Immortal Technique","answerA":"Immortal Technique","answerB":"Slick Rick","answerC":"LL Cool J","answerD":"Master P"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The American rapper and political activist Talib Kweli teamed up with Mos Def in 1997 to form this influential hip-hop group.","correct":"Black Star","answerA":"Black Star","answerB":"Wu-Tang Clan","answerC":"Black Sheep","answerD":"Onyx"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- In the 1993 Cypress Hill song \\"I Want to Get High\\" which politician did the group encourage to \\"go and inhale?\\" ","correct":"Bill Clinton","answerA":"Bill Clinton","answerB":"John Edwards","answerC":"Gary Hart","answerD":"Al Gore"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- LA based hip-hop artist and community activist Nipsey Hussle was murdered in March 2019. How old was he?","correct":"33","answerA":"33","answerB":"27","answerC":"53","answerD":"19"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The Root\'s 4th studio album Things Fall Apart took its name from a 1958 book from which political Nigerian writer?","correct":"Chinua Achebe","answerA":"Chinua Achebe","answerB":"Kwame Nkrumah","answerC":"Wole Soyinka","answerD":"Franz Fanon"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Afrika Bambaataa, widely considered the\xa0creator of electro- funk and an influential hip- hop innovator, founded what South Bronx based hip- hop organization in 1973","correct":"The Universal Zulu Nation","answerA":"The Universal Zulu Nation","answerB":"Boogie Down Productions","answerC":"Hip Hop Congress","answerD":"Hip Hop for Change"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Jay- Z has funded a number of social causes including this\xa0group dedicated to criminal justice reform. What\'s the name of the organization?","correct":"Reform Alliance","answerA":"Reform Alliance","answerB":"Prison Abolition Committee","answerC":"Criminal Justice Task Force","answerD":"End Mass Incarceration Now!"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This Dr. Dre prot\xe9g\xe9 came out in support of Colin Kaepernick and his symbolic protest against police brutality at the BET Hip-Hop Awards in 2017.","correct":"Eminem","answerA":"Eminem","answerB":"Snoop Dogg","answerC":"Easy E","answerD":"DJ Yella"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- MMG was a Revolutionary Communist Party affiliated hip-hop collective from New York that recorded this pro-U.S. flag burning song back in 1990.","correct":"\\"Burn Baby Burn\\"","answerA":"\\"Burn Baby Burn\\"","answerB":"\\"50 State Fire\\"","answerC":"\\"Old Glory in Flames\\"","answerD":"\\"Burn the Flag\\""},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Which Vice President went on TV to attack Tupac Shakar\'s first album 2pacalypse Now in 1991 blaming it for a police officer\'s death in Texas.","correct":"Dan Quayle","answerA":"Dan Quayle","answerB":"Nelson Rockefeller","answerC":"Dick Cheney","answerD":"Al Gore"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- On March 18 2016, 13 swat team members with the Fayetteville police department raided this rappers recording studio in North Carolina. Who was it?","correct":"J. Cole","answerA":"J. Cole","answerB":"21 Savage","answerC":"Drake","answerD":"Kendrick Lamar"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Which Black nationalist poetry group appeared on the A Tribe Called Quest song  \\"Excursions\\" off their 1991 masterpiece The Low End Theory? ","correct":"The Last Poets","answerA":"The Last Poets","answerB":"The Black Kings","answerC":"The Black Notes","answerD":"The Last Negros"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- What was the name of the anti-violence song that the West Coast Rap All-Stars dropped in 1990?","correct":"\\"We\'re All in the Same Gang\\"","answerA":"\\"We\'re All in the Same Gang\\"","answerB":"\\"No Justice, Just Us\\"","answerC":"\\"They Just See Black\\"","answerD":"\\"Stop Killing Your Brothers\\""},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- In 2017 this Muslim rapper from Flint, Michigan released a song defending women who choose to wear Hijabs called \\"Hijabi (Wrap my Hijab).\\" What\'s her name?","correct":"Mona Hayder","answerA":"Mona Hayder","answerB":"Mayam Mahmoud","answerC":"Shadia Mansour","answerD":"Felukah"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Bronx based, female rapper Cardi B endorsed this candidate for president in 2020.","correct":"Bernie Sanders","answerA":"Bernie Sanders","answerB":"Elizabeth Warren","answerC":"Andrew Yang","answerD":"Kamala Harris"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- What\'s the name of the Philadelphia based alternative hip-hop group The Goats second album?","correct":"No Goats, No Glory","answerA":"No Goats, No Glory","answerB":"Tricks of the Shade","answerC":"Typical American","answerD":"Rumblefish"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The song \\"Self Destruction,\\" a late \'80\'s rap song that spoke out against black on black violence, was created by the Stop the Violence Movement. Who started it?","correct":"KRS-One","answerA":"KRS-One","answerB":"George Clinton","answerC":"Chuck D","answerD":"Afrika Bambaataa"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This member of the groundbreaking New York hip-hop group the Fugees decided to return to their birthplace, Haiti, in 2010 and run for president.","correct":"Wyclef Jean","answerA":"Wyclef Jean","answerB":"Pras Michel","answerC":"Lauryn Hill","answerD":"Chris Schwartz"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Jay-Z called out Al Sharpton in this hip-hop track for scapegoating rap music for promoting negative stereotypes of urban blacks.","correct":"\\"Say Hello\\"","answerA":"\\"Say Hello\\"","answerB":"\\"99 Problems\\"","answerC":"\\"Drop it Like its Hot\\"","answerD":"\\"Frontin\'\\""},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The late Lumumba Carson, better known as Professor X the Overseer, was a black nationalist, Brooklyn based rapper with what group in the late 1980\'s and early 90\'s?","correct":"X-Clan","answerA":"X-Clan","answerB":"Poor Righteous Teachers","answerC":"Brand Nubian","answerD":"The Last Poets"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Hip-Hop artist Jay-Z endorsed this political leader for president in 2008.","correct":"Barack Obama","answerA":"Barack Obama","answerB":"John Edwards","answerC":"Alan Keyes","answerD":"Hillary Clinton"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Ice Cube\'s second album, an incendiary black nationalist, hip-hop classic,  debuted at number one on the Billboard charts. What was it?","correct":"Death Certificate","answerA":"Death Certificate","answerB":"War and Peace Volume 1","answerC":"The Predator","answerD":"Amerikkka\'s Most Wanted"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The famous film maker Spike Lee partnered with this political hip-hip group in the late 1980\'s to produce the main song- \\"Fight the Power\\"- in the sound track to his movie Do the Right Thing. ","correct":"Public Enemy","answerA":"Public Enemy","answerB":"Run-DMC","answerC":"Paris","answerD":"X-Clan"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The southern rap artist Lil Wayne wrote the song \\"Georgia Bush\\" in 2007 in response to what event?","correct":"Hurricane Katrina","answerA":"Hurricane Katrina","answerB":"The mass shooting at Fort Hood","answerC":"The surge of combat troops in Iraq","answerD":"The Georgia Tech mass shooting"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- How many pages did the FBI have on Tupac Shakar right before his death?","correct":"4,000","answerA":"4,000","answerB":"7,800","answerC":"200","answerD":"4"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The hip-Hop artist Common wrote \\"A Song for Assata\\" in 2000. Assata Shakur was a member of what black liberation organization of the 1970\'s and 80\'s?","correct":"Black Liberation Army","answerA":"Black Liberation Army","answerB":"Blackstone Rangers","answerC":"Nation of Islam","answerD":"Black Panther Party"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This former member of the Geto Boys wrote the song \\"Fuck Rodney King\\" in response to King\'s timid reaction to the not guilty verdicts related to his own brutal beating by the police","correct":"Willie D","answerA":"Willie D","answerB":"Bushwick Bill","answerC":"Master P","answerD":"Scarface"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The song Steve Biko (Stir it Up) by A Tribe Called Quest appeared on what 1993 album of theirs?","correct":"Midnight Marauders","answerA":"Midnight Marauders","answerB":"The Love Movement","answerC":"The Low End Theory","answerD":"Beats Rhymes & Life"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The 1991 rap hit \\"Free South Africa\\" appeared on which Stetsasonic album? ","correct":"Blood, Sweat and no Tears","answerA":"Blood, Sweat and no Tears","answerB":"Just Say Stet","answerC":"In Full Gear","answerD":"On Fire"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This feminist, sex positive, hip-hop trio won a Grammy for the 1995 song \\"None of Your Business.\\"","correct":"Salt-N-Pepa","answerA":"Salt-N-Pepa","answerB":"The Mercedes Ladies","answerC":"Destiny\'s Child","answerD":"SWV"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Members of Public Enemy and Rage Against the Machine got together with this LA based hip-hop group in 2007 to create the group Prophets of Rage.","correct":"Cypress Hill","answerA":"Cypress Hill","answerB":"Ozomatli","answerC":"Da Lynch Mob","answerD":"Dilated Peoples"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The Arrested Development song \\"Revolution\\" appeared on what 1992 album? ","correct":"The soundtrack to the movie Malcolm X","answerA":"The soundtrack to the movie Malcolm X","answerB":"The soundtrack to the movie Menace II Society","answerC":"The soundtrack to the movie Black Panther","answerD":"The soundtrack to the movie Boyz in the Hood"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This Denver based indy hip- hop anarchist released the 2013 album No Wising Up, No Settling Down in which he declared \\"I Think I\'m Emma Goldman.\\"","correct":"Sole","answerA":"Sole","answerB":"Macklemore","answerC":"J. Cole","answerD":"emcee lynx"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- What year was the classic reality rap song \\"The Message\\" by Grand Master Flash and the Furious Five released? ","correct":"1981","answerA":"1981","answerB":"1973","answerC":"2011","answerD":"2005"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- The Peruvian American political hip-hop artist Immortal Technique appeared in this movie drama about the 2004 Republican National Convention in New York City.","correct":"This Revolution","answerA":"This Revolution","answerB":"My Revolution","answerC":"Revolution Now","answerD":"Our Revolution"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- What Bronx based political rapper started the label Boogie Down Productions with the late Scott La Rock?","correct":"KRS-One","answerA":"KRS-One","answerB":"Kool Moe Dee","answerC":"Nas","answerD":"Kool G Rap"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This US based rapper was the first female, solo, hip-hop artist to release a full rap album in 1988. Who is she?","correct":"MC Lyte","answerA":"MC Lyte","answerB":"The Lady of Rage","answerC":"Queen Latifah","answerD":"Yo-Yo"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- This Philadelphia based hip hop artist who got trapped in Pennsylvania\'s criminal justice system based on a wrongful arrest at 19, started the Reform Alliance with Jay Z.","correct":"Meek Mill","answerA":"Meek Mill","answerB":"Schoolly D","answerC":"Steady B","answerD":"Black Thought"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- What was the underling point of Tupac Shakur\'s \\"Thug Life\\" philosophy? ","correct":"To politicize black street gangs across the US","answerA":"To politicize black street gangs across the US","answerB":"To unite all motorcycle gangs across all races","answerC":"To encourage friendship between Blacks and Latinos","answerD":"To encourage blacks to start their own businesses"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Which record label first distributed the conscious hip-hop and world music artist Michael Franti?","correct":"Alternative Tentacles","answerA":"Alternative Tentacles","answerB":"Anti-","answerC":"Six Degrees Records","answerD":"Capitol"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Black America Again, released in 2016, was the 11th studio album by which political hip-hop artist?","correct":"Common","answerA":"Common","answerB":"Drake","answerC":"Usher","answerD":"John Legend"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Sinead O Conner teamed up with this rap artist in 1988 for the sex positive song  \\"I Want Your (Hands on Me.)\\" ","correct":"MC Lyte","answerA":"MC Lyte","answerB":"Left Eye (Lisa Lopes)","answerC":"Missy Elliott","answerD":"Monie Love"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Poor Righteous Teachers, a socially conscious hip-hop group big in the late 80\'s and 90\'s, were a part of what New York based soci-spiritual movement?","correct":"The Five Percent Nation","answerA":"The Five Percent Nation","answerB":"The Three Percent Nation","answerC":"The 10 Percent Nation","answerD":"The One Percent Nation"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Afrika Bambaataa teamed up with former Sex Pistols singer Johnny Lydon in 1984 to record the anti-fascist, anti-racist classic \\"World Destruction.\\" What was the name of their group?","correct":"Time Zone","answerA":"Time Zone","answerB":"War Zone","answerC":"Fight Zone","answerD":"Death Zone"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- Lauryn Hill performed the song \\"I Find it Hard to Say (Rebel)\\" in a memorable performance on which show in 2002?","correct":"MTV Unplugged","answerA":"MTV Unplugged","answerB":"In Living Color","answerC":"Saturday Night Live","answerD":"The Arsenio Hall Show"},{"question":"REBEL RAPPERS- What\'s the name East Bay rapper Paris\'s first album?","correct":"The Devil Made Me Do It","answerA":"The Devil Made Me Do It","answerB":"Sonic Jihad","answerC":"Sleeping With the Enemy","answerD":"Acid Reflex"}]')},45:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- At a 2019 Kennedy Center Honors event the then Secretary of State Mike Pompeo was called out by this 70\'s era soft-rock singer and honoree for being an enabler to President Trump.","correct":"Linda Ronstadt","answerA":"Linda Ronstadt","answerB":"Debbie Boone","answerC":"Joan Biaz","answerD":"Olivia Newton- John"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 2001 this norte\xf1o band from San Jos\xe9, California sang \\"Let me remind the gringo, that I didn\'t cross the border, the border crossed me.\\"","correct":"Los Tigres del Norte","answerA":"Los Tigres del Norte","answerB":"Los Tucanes de Tijuana","answerC":"Intocable","answerD":"Vicente \\"Chente\\" Fern\xe1ndez "},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 1985 what British weekly music magazine voted the landmark political album \\"What\'s Going On\\" by Marvin Gaye the best album of all time? ","correct":"NME","answerA":"NME","answerB":"The Globe","answerC":"Melody Maker","answerD":"Melody Maker"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who is considered the first author of the 1901 civil rights anthem \\"We Shall Overcome\\"? ","correct":"Claude McKay","answerA":"Claude McKay","answerB":"Charles Tindley","answerC":"Countee Cullen","answerD":"James Weldon Johnson"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This folk punk artist, and champion of feminist causes, began her music career by starting her own record label- Righteous Babe Records. Who is the Artist?","correct":"Ani DiFranco","answerA":"Ani DiFranco","answerB":"Lucinda Williams","answerC":"Tori Amos","answerD":"Laura Jane Grace"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What year did the Temptations song about the sad state of the world \\"Ball of Confusion\\" come out?","correct":"1970","answerA":"1970","answerB":"1943","answerC":"1990","answerD":"1964"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The synth- rock band Depeche Mode released this atheist friendly hit in 1984 that mocked \\"God\'s sick sense of humor.\\" ","correct":"\\"Blasphemous Rumors\\"","answerA":"\\"Blasphemous Rumors\\"","answerB":"\\"Master and Servant\\"","answerC":"\\"Flies on the Windscreen\\"","answerD":"\\"Personal Jesus\\""},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The 1986 album Lives in the Balance, a record full of songs critical of U.S. imperialism and militarism, is perhaps the most political album by this U.S. rock musician and singer.","correct":"Jackson Brown","answerA":"Jackson Brown","answerB":"James Taylor","answerC":"Don Henley","answerD":"Tom Petty"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This female R&B artist from Texas was arrested in 2010, and charged with disorderly conduct for appearing nude in Dealey Plaza in Dallas for a video shoot.","correct":"Erykah Badu","answerA":"Erykah Badu","answerB":"Jill Scott","answerC":"Mary J Blige","answerD":"Lauryn Hill"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This artist recorded the song \\"Freedom is Free\\" in 2017 to counter the notion that war and death are necessary costs for freedom. ","correct":"Chicano Batman","answerA":"Chicano Batman","answerB":"Ozomatli","answerC":"Bardo Martinez","answerD":"Styx"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Nina Hagen\'s 1983 hit \\"99 Red Balloons\\" was about what? ","correct":"Cold war paranoia","answerA":"Cold war paranoia","answerB":"Fascist paranoia","answerC":"White supremacist paranoia","answerD":"War on terror paranoia"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- How did the radical, folk musician Phil Ochs die?","correct":"Suicide","answerA":"Suicide","answerB":"Murder","answerC":"AIDS","answerD":"Cancer"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The country singer Tim McGraw described himself as what type of Democrat in 2008?","correct":"Blue Dog","answerA":"Blue Dog","answerB":"Southern","answerC":"Conservative","answerD":"Progressive"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Donna Summer and  Barbara Streisand teamed up to record this women\'s rights song in 1979.","correct":"\\"No More Tears (Enough is Enough)\\"","answerA":"\\"No More Tears (Enough is Enough)\\"","answerB":"\\"(I\'m a) Stand Up Women\\"","answerC":"\\"I Am a Women\\"","answerD":"\\"I Will Survive LA\\""},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This folk rock duo performed a concert in the spring in 2016 to protest the United Methodist Church\'s ban on  permitting same-sex couples to marry.","correct":"Indigo Girls","answerA":"Indigo Girls","answerB":"Ann and Nancy Wilson","answerC":"Shakespeare\'s Sister","answerD":"Ann and Nancy Wilson"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This famous 1970\'s pop and blues singer said in 2018;  \\"There\'s climate in the Republican Party of complicity with the leader of the country, who is inspiring people to violence.\\"","correct":"Carol King","answerA":"Carol King","answerB":"Debbie Boone","answerC":"Anne Murray","answerD":"Carly Simon"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This best selling singer, popular in the 1970\'s and early 80\'s, was a big supporter of Bill Clinton in his 1992 bid for the White House and became a close family friend.","correct":"Barbara Streisand","answerA":"Barbara Streisand","answerB":"Bette Midler","answerC":"Cher","answerD":"Liza Minelli"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Avant Grade singer Diamanda Gal\xe1s was a member of what direct action organization in the 1980\'s?","correct":"ACT UP","answerA":"ACT UP","answerB":"The National Organization of Women","answerC":"Queer Nation","answerD":"Human Rights Campaign"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who started Band Aid?","correct":"Bob Geldof and Midge Ure","answerA":"Bob Geldof and Midge Ure","answerB":"Boy George and Midge Ure","answerC":"Bono and Jim Kerr","answerD":"Bob Geldof and Bono"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Which black female singing group recorded the song \\"Independent Women (Part 1)\\"? ","correct":"Destiny\'s Child","answerA":"Destiny\'s Child","answerB":"TLC","answerC":"Salt -n- Pepa","answerD":"En Vouge"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What\'s the name of radical folk singer Billy Bragg\'s first album?","correct":"Life\'s Riot With Spy vs Spy","answerA":"Life\'s Riot With Spy vs Spy","answerB":"Don\'t Try This at Home","answerC":"England, Half English","answerD":"Worker\'s Playtime"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This androgynous hip-hop, and psychedelic soul artist has been considered a lead innovator in the afro-futurist movement.","correct":"Janelle Monae","answerA":"Janelle Monae","answerB":"Grace Jones","answerC":"Cynthia Erivo","answerD":"Tessa Thompson"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The folk trio Peter, Paul and Mary recorded the top ten hit \\"If I Had a Hammer\\" in 1962. Who originally wrote the song?","correct":"Pete Seeger and Lee Hayes","answerA":"Pete Seeger and Lee Hayes","answerB":"Woody Guthrie","answerC":"Phil Ochs","answerD":"Millard Lampell and Bob Dylan"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What year did the all gay, synth trio Bronski Beat form in England?","correct":"1983","answerA":"1983","answerB":"1990","answerC":"1967","answerD":"2010"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 1939 the organization Daughters of the American Revolution refused to let this black opera singer perform at their concert venue, Constitution Hall, because she was black.","correct":"Marian Anderson","answerA":"Marian Anderson","answerB":"Sarah Vaughan","answerC":"Lena Horne","answerD":"Ella Fitzgerald"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- America singer Lena Horne, worked with this first lady in the 1940\'s around anti-lynching legislation.","correct":"Elenore Roosevelt","answerA":"Elenore Roosevelt","answerB":"Lou Henry Hoover","answerC":"Mamie Eisenhower","answerD":"Bess Truman"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In Madonna\'s 1989 video like \\"Like a Prayer\\" a black man is falsely arrested for what? ","correct":"Killing a white girl","answerA":"Killing a white girl","answerB":"Marrying a white girl in the 1920\'s","answerC":"Raping a white girl","answerD":"Staring at a white girl"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The song \\"Why?\\", a 1984 hit song by the group Bronski Beat about anti-gay prejudice and hate appeared on what important album?","correct":"Age of Consent","answerA":"Age of Consent","answerB":"Truthdare Doubledare","answerC":"Rainbow Nation","answerD":"Red"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What year did the music effort \\"Band Aid\\" begin? ","correct":"1984","answerA":"1984","answerB":"1999","answerC":"1971","answerD":"2013"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The jazz oratorio piece \\"Blood on the Fields\\" about black chattel slavery in the U.S. was written by which jazz traditionalist popular in the early 1980\'s? ","correct":"Wynton Marsalis","answerA":"Wynton Marsalis","answerB":"Herbie Hancock","answerC":"Miles Davis","answerD":"Wayne Shorter"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Dr. Bernice Johnson Reagon founded this  all-female, African-American cappella ensemble.","correct":"Sweet Honey in the Rock","answerA":"Sweet Honey in the Rock","answerB":"The Shirelles","answerC":"The Supremes","answerD":"The Chiffons"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What train did the British singer and song writer Cat Stevens want people to get on in 1971?","correct":"The peace train","answerA":"The peace train","answerB":"The party train","answerC":"The last train","answerD":"The A train"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 1986 Nina Hagen teamed up with this new wave artist to record the song \\"Don\'t Kill the Animals.\\" Who was the other musician?","correct":"Lene Lovich","answerA":"Lene Lovich","answerB":"Laurie Anderson","answerC":"Joan Jett","answerD":"Debbie Harry"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- New York singer Diamanda Gal\xe1s\'s Masque of the Red Death, released in 1989 was about what subject?","correct":"The AIDS crisis","answerA":"The AIDS crisis","answerB":"The West Nile Virus","answerC":"The COVID 19 Virus","answerD":"The Ebola Virus"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What was the name of country singer/ songwriter Steve Earle\'s 2004 song about revolution?","correct":"\\"The Revolution Starts Now\\"","answerA":"\\"The Revolution Starts Now\\"","answerB":"\\"I Am the Revolution\\"","answerC":"\\"I\'m Waiting For the Revolution\\"","answerD":"\\"We are the Revolution\\""},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Salman Ramadan Abedi killed 23 people and wounded over 139 at a May 22, 2017 pop concert in a bombing attack in Manchester, England. Who was the performer?","correct":"Ariana Grande","answerA":"Ariana Grande","answerB":"Lady Gaga","answerC":"J- Lo","answerD":"Selena Gomez"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The title of the Michael Eric Dyson book \\"Make Me Wanna Holla\\" was taken from what artist\'s 1971 song? ","correct":"Marvin Gaye/ Inner City Blues","answerA":"Marvin Gaye/ Inner City Blues","answerB":"Smokey Robinson/ Holla","answerC":"Stevie Wonder/ Livin\' for the City","answerD":"Jackie Wilson/ Throw up My Hand"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What label did the funk, rock, and R&B musician Me\'Shell NdegeOcello sign with in the early 1990\'s?","correct":"Maverick Records","answerA":"Maverick Records","answerB":"Sony Records","answerC":"2- Tone Records","answerD":"Arista Records"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Swing Low, Sweet Cadillac, a 1967 live recording from American jazz trumpeter Dizzy Gillespie was about what?","correct":"The cultural journey of black slaves in the U.S. from an African identity to an American one.","answerA":"The cultural journey of black slaves in the U.S. from an African identity to an American one.","answerB":"The end of African American slavery in the United States in 1965 and its aftermath","answerC":"The music revolution that started in Motown Detriot- the manufacturing center of Cadillac","answerD":"The horrors of the Middle Passage for African slaves in their transport to the U.S."},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This 2017 album by Hurry for the Riff Raff contained the alternative hit \\"Palante\\", about the struggles of everyday peoples in the face of colonialism from a Puerto Rican perspective.","correct":"The Navigator","answerA":"The Navigator","answerB":"Look Out Mama","answerC":"My Dearest Darkest","answerD":"Small Town Heroes"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Which country singer said in 2015 \\"I\'m a great Bernie and Hillary fan, you know?\\"","correct":"Willie Nelson","answerA":"Willie Nelson","answerB":"Tim McGraw","answerC":"Toby Keith","answerD":"Keith Urban"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The 1970 song \\"Big Yellow Taxi\\" by folk singer-songwriter Joni Mitchell was about what?","correct":"Environmental  Degradation","answerA":"Environmental  Degradation","answerB":"Car Pollution","answerC":"Racism in Canada","answerD":"The Evils of War"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- \\"Strange Fruit\\", a song about Black lynching\'s in the U.S., was recorded by this female jazz singer in 1939.","correct":"Billy Holiday","answerA":"Billy Holiday","answerB":"Ella Fitzgerald","answerC":"Sarah Vaughan","answerD":"Etta James"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- During a 1977 episode of Sesame Street, who participated in the first representation of breastfeeding ever aired on television?","correct":"Buffy Sainte- Marie","answerA":"Buffy Sainte- Marie","answerB":"Loretta Lynn","answerC":"Linda Ronstadt","answerD":"Olivia Newton-John"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 2019 the record Omoiyari, a concept album about the internment of Japanese Americans during World War II, was released by which Seattle based violinist?","correct":"Kishi Bashi","answerA":"Kishi Bashi","answerB":"Haruomi Hosono","answerC":"Keiji Haino","answerD":"Ami Nakashima"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Annie Lennox, of the synth- pop duo the Eurythmics, partnered with this soul music legend to record the feminist song \\"Sisters Are Doing it For Themselves.\\"","correct":"Aretha Franklin","answerA":"Aretha Franklin","answerB":"Diana Ross","answerC":"Celine Dion","answerD":"Mariah Carey"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This U.S. composer and innovator in experimental music declared in an 1985 interview that he was an anarchist stating \\"I don\'t like government! And I don\'t like institutions!\\"","correct":"John Cage","answerA":"John Cage","answerB":"Phillip Glass","answerC":"Bryan Ferry","answerD":"Brian Eno"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This influential, Black blues singer and guitarist from Birmingham, Alabama sang \\"O\'freedom\\" at the historic March on Washington for civil rights and jobs.","correct":"Odetta","answerA":"Odetta","answerB":"Lena Horne","answerC":"Eartha Kitt","answerD":"Etta James"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This singer/songwriter released the women\'s liberation anthem \\"I am Women\\" in 1971. What\'s her name?","correct":"Hellen Reddy","answerA":"Hellen Reddy","answerB":"Olivia Newton- John","answerC":"Anne Murray","answerD":"Leslie Gore"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The U.S. based, 1970\'s funk band Roy C. Hammond and the Honey Drippers released the song \\"Impeach the President.\\" What president did they want impeached?","correct":"Richard Nixon","answerA":"Richard Nixon","answerB":"George W Bush","answerC":"Bill Clinton","answerD":"Gerald Ford"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This folk and blues singer who wrote songs about prison, slavery and being poor and black in the south, was convicted of murder and attempted murder in the early 1900\'s.","correct":"Lead Belly","answerA":"Lead Belly","answerB":"Howling Wolf","answerC":"Muddy Waters","answerD":"Willie Dixon"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Dionne Warwick recorded this song in 1962 expressing frustration at men in the music industry trying to mold her into something she wasn\'t. What was the song?","correct":"\\"Don\'t Make Me Over\\"","answerA":"\\"Don\'t Make Me Over\\"","answerB":"\\"You Don\'t Know Me\\"","answerC":"\\"I am Me\\"","answerD":"\\"I Am Who I Am\\""},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Female R&B artist Erykah Badu is a member of what socio-spiritual movement?","correct":"The Five Percent Nation","answerA":"The Five Percent Nation","answerB":"The Santeria Religion","answerC":"The Fruit of Islam","answerD":"The Pentecostals"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The Stevie Wonder song \\"Livin\' for the City\\", a song about the struggles of poor, black inner city youth and the racist system of mass incarceration, first appeared on what 1973 album?","correct":"Innervisions","answerA":"Innervisions","answerB":"Songs in the Key of Life","answerC":"My Cherie Amour","answerD":"Talking Book"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 1968 the\xa0\\"Godfather of Soul\\"\xa0James Brown released an anthem of the Black Power movement. What song was it? ","correct":"\\"Say it Loud I\'m Black and I\'m Proud\\"","answerA":"\\"Say it Loud I\'m Black and I\'m Proud\\"","answerB":"\\"I\'ve Got You (I Feel Good)\\"","answerC":"\\"Papa\'s Got a Brand New Bag\\"","answerD":"\\"Get Up Offa That Thing\\""},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What two groups named their records \\"Steal This Album\\" after the 1960\'s YIPPIE Abbie Hoffman\'s \\"Steal this Book.\\" ","correct":"The political hip-hop group the Coup and the alternative metal band System of a Down","answerA":"The political hip-hop group the Coup and the alternative metal band System of a Down","answerB":"The political hip- hop group Dead  Prez and the alternative metal band Rage Against the Machine","answerC":"The hip-hop group The Roots and the alternative metal band Faith No More","answerD":"The hip-hop group Gang Star and the alternative metal band Insane Clown Posse"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who wrote and sang \\"People Get Ready\\", a warm and soulful song released in 1965, inspired by the US  civil rights movement?","correct":"Curtis Mayfield","answerA":"Curtis Mayfield","answerB":"Marvin Gaye","answerC":"Al Green","answerD":"Isaac Hayes"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who sang these lyrics in the 1971 song \\"Man in Black\\"? \\"I wear the black for the poor and beaten down/living in the hopeless, hungry side of town/I wear it for the prisoner who has long paid for his crime/but is there because he\'s a victim of the time.\\"","correct":"Johnny Cash","answerA":"Johnny Cash","answerB":"Waylon Jennings","answerC":"Merle Haggard","answerD":"Kris Kristofferson"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The androgynous new wave and soul artist Grace Jones was born in what country?","correct":"Jamaica","answerA":"Jamaica","answerB":"Trinidad and Tobago","answerC":"Dominican Republic","answerD":"Haiti"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Former four term governor of California, Jerry Brown, dated this U.S. based soft-rock singer popular in the 1970\'s.","correct":"Linda Ronstadt","answerA":"Linda Ronstadt","answerB":"Bette Midler","answerC":"Chaka Kahn","answerD":"Patti LaBelle"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The song \\"Hello Birmingham\\" by radical punk folk artist Ani DiFranco is about what?","correct":"The 1998 bombing of an abortion clinic in Birmingham, Alabama","answerA":"The 1998 bombing of an abortion clinic in Birmingham, Alabama","answerB":"The racist bombing of a Black Church in Birmingham, Alabama","answerC":"The murder of Kansas abortion provider George Tiller in 2009","answerD":"The murder of Florida abortion provider Dr. David Gunn in 1993"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who recorded the 1960 American jazz album \\"We Insist! Freedom Now\\" ","correct":"Max Roach","answerA":"Max Roach","answerB":"Buddy Rich","answerC":"Neil Peart","answerD":"Art Blakey"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Aretha Franklin released the feminist anthem \\"Respect\\" in what year?","correct":"1967","answerA":"1967","answerB":"1950","answerC":"1995","answerD":"2003"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The 1931 organized labor staple \\"I Am a Union Women\\" was written and sang by who?","correct":"Aunt Molly Jackson","answerA":"Aunt Molly Jackson","answerB":"Bessie Smith","answerC":"Sara Carter","answerD":"Marion Harris"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Donna Summer sang this controversial song in 1978 about sex workers in LA. What was the name of the song?","correct":"\\"Bad Girls\\"","answerA":"\\"Bad Girls\\"","answerB":"\\"Dim all the Lights\\"","answerC":"\\"MacArthur Park\\"","answerD":"\\"Hot Stuff\\""},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In October 2018 this pop artist is generally credited with registering over 166,000 voters across the US with one Instagram message in the run up to election day.","correct":"Taylor Swift","answerA":"Taylor Swift","answerB":"Selena Gomez","answerC":"Beyonce","answerD":"Lady Gaga"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- According to Leonard Cohen in this 1992 song off his album The Future what is coming to USA?","correct":"Democracy","answerA":"Democracy","answerB":"Fascism","answerC":"Socialism","answerD":"A Race War"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In what year did Sweet Honey in the Rock perform at the Obama White House?","correct":"2008","answerA":"2008","answerB":"1999","answerC":"2017","answerD":"2005"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In 2018 pop singer John Legend came out in support of what Florida state ballot measure?","correct":"Amendment 4 to restore voting rights to ex-prison","answerA":"Amendment 4 to restore voting rights to ex-prison","answerB":"ACT 12 to reinstate affirmative action in","answerC":"Initiative 204 to ban discrimination against LGBTQ in employment","answerD":"Measure 13 to ban undocumented immigrants from voting"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Which famous, Canadian born, folk and jazz singer-songwriter wrote the 1970 song \\"Woodstock\\"?","correct":"Joni Mitchell","answerA":"Joni Mitchell","answerB":"Janis Joplin","answerC":"Mama Cass","answerD":"Carol Carpenter"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- The pop star Lady Gaga won the MTV Video Music Award for Best Female Video in 2011 for this pro LGBTQI song.","correct":"\\"Born This Way\\"","answerA":"\\"Born This Way\\"","answerB":"\\"I\'m Coming Out\\"","answerC":"\\"Hair\\"","answerD":"\\"Kiss Me I\'m Queer\\""},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- This former boy band superstar was arrested on stage in Georgia for simulating sex on a bed with audience members.","correct":"Bobby Brown","answerA":"Bobby Brown","answerB":"Donnie Wahlberg","answerC":"Joe Jonas","answerD":"Chris Sellers"},{"question":"REBEL MUISC MIX- In 1996, she started a philanthropic non-profit fund Nihewan Foundation for American Indian Education devoted to improving Native American students participation in learning.","correct":"Buffy Sainte-Marie","answerA":"Buffy Sainte-Marie","answerB":"Joni Michell","answerC":"Tanya Tagaq","answerD":"Joan Baez"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What\'s the name of the Mitt Romney dog that the new wave band Devo sang about wanting to save from the roof of his car on family outings during the 2012 presidential race?","correct":"Seamus","answerA":"Seamus","answerB":"Mutt","answerC":"Goldwater","answerD":"Brigham"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Who wrote and recorded the song \\"Talkin about a Revolution\\" in 1988? ","correct":"Tracy Chapman","answerA":"Tracy Chapman","answerB":"Mary J Blige","answerC":"Macy Gray","answerD":"Suzanne Vega"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- What smooth 1960\'s R&B artist recorded the civil rights anthem \\"A Change is Gonna Come\\"?","correct":"Sam Cooke","answerA":"Sam Cooke","answerB":"Barry White","answerC":"Otis Redding","answerD":"Wilson Pickett"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Winona LaDuke, a Native American activist and former Green Party candidate for office, worked with this folk rock duo to start the grassroots environmental group Honor the Earth.","correct":"Indigo Girls","answerA":"Indigo Girls","answerB":"Simon and  Garfunkel","answerC":"Captain and Tennille","answerD":"Hall and Oats"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- In the 1971 classic album \\"What\'s Going On\\" this soul artist tackles everything from racism to the Vietnam War to environmental degradation. Who was the artist? ","correct":"Marvin Gaye","answerA":"Marvin Gaye","answerB":"Curtis Mayfield","answerC":"Smoky Robinson","answerD":"Peter Frampton"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- How old was the pop singer Leslie Gore when she recorded the early women\'s lib hit \\"You Don\'t Own Me\\" in 1963?","correct":"17","answerA":"17","answerB":"30","answerC":"45","answerD":"13"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Which one of these bands never released a song about a \\"racist friend?\\"","correct":"Rise Against","answerA":"Rise Against","answerB":"They Might Be Giants","answerC":"Naomi Pilgrim","answerD":"Special AKA"},{"question":"REBEL MUSIC MIX- Finish the title of this Joe Hill song written in 1913 and covered in 1984 by Billy Bragg. \\"There is power in a _______\\"? ","correct":"union","answerA":"union","answerB":"friendship","answerC":"nation","answerD":"family"}]')},46:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"RAD ROUND- This U.S. president once told radio broadcasters that rock lyrics should be screened for content and that any music containing drug references should be banned.","correct":"Richard Nixon","answerA":"Richard Nixon","answerB":"Donald Trump","answerC":"Ronald Reagan","answerD":"George W Bush","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- \\"House Burning Down\\", a 1970 song critical of rioters who burn down their own neighborhoods to protest racial injustice, was written and performed by who?","correct":"Jimi Hendricks","answerA":"Jimi Hendricks","answerB":"Carlos Santana","answerC":"Eric Clapton","answerD":"Sly Stone","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- This member of Rage Against the Machine was arrested with Union of Garment Worker organizers in 1997 for civil disobedience in Santa Monica protesting the use of sweatshop labor by the clothing company Guess.","correct":"Tom Morello","answerA":"Tom Morello","answerB":"Zack de la Rocha","answerC":"Tim Commerford","answerD":"Brad Wilk","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- This founder of the afro-beat genre was arrested about 200 times by the Nigerian police and military forces due to his political activism and his socially conscious music.","correct":"Fela Kuti","answerA":"Fela Kuti","answerB":"King Sunny Ad\xe9","answerC":"Sun Ra","answerD":"Femi Kuti","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- Why did Jessie Jackson call for a radio station ban on disco music in 1977?","correct":"Because it promotes promiscuity and drug use.","answerA":"Because it promotes promiscuity and drug use.","answerB":"Because it exploits, and demeans women and girls","answerC":"Because Black musicians were getting discriminated against with pay.","answerD":"Because it promoted negative stereotypes of Blacks and gays","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- In 1971 the popular funk band Sly and the Family Stone released their 5th studio album. What was the title of the record?","correct":"There\'s a Riot Goin On","answerA":"There\'s a Riot Goin On","answerB":"Stand","answerC":"Fresh","answerD":"Life","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- In what country did a group of teenagers receive 91 lashes and 6 months in jail in 2014 for making a video of themselves dancing to the Pharrell William\'s song \\"Happy\\"?","correct":"Iran","answerA":"Iran","answerB":"Saudi Arabia","answerC":"China","answerD":"Singapore","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- This radical 1960\'s musician from Chile once said \\"The authentic revolutionary should be behind a guitar, so the guitar becomes an instrument of struggle, so  it... shoot[s] like a gun.\\"","correct":"Victor Jara","answerA":"Victor Jara","answerB":"Silvio Rodr\xedguez","answerC":"Atahualpa Yupanqui","answerD":"Eduardo Carrasco","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- This 1950\'s DJ refused to play white cover versions of black songs, in  protest of racial segregation in broadcast radio.","correct":"Alan Freed","answerA":"Alan Freed","answerB":"Howard Stern","answerC":"Dick Clark","answerD":"Wolfman Jack","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- The David Bowie record \\"Rebel Rebel,\\" a 1974 song about a cross dressing youth who wears tacky women\'s cloths, appears on what album?","correct":"Diamond Dogs","answerA":"Diamond Dogs","answerB":"Aladdin Sane","answerC":"Young Americans","answerD":"Station to Station","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- This radical folk singer refused to cooperate with the House of Unamerican Activities Committee in their witch-hunt against communists in 1955 and was sentenced to a year in jail.","correct":"Pete Seeger","answerA":"Pete Seeger","answerB":"Utah Phillips","answerC":"Lead Belly","answerD":"Mary Travers","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- The Clash\'s 4th album was named after a successful socialist revolution in Central America in 1979. What was the name of the album?","correct":"Sandinista!","answerA":"Sandinista!","answerB":"London Calling","answerC":"Combat Rock","answerD":"Give Em Enough Rope","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- Which famous beat poet appeared in Bob Dylan\'s \\"Subterranean Homesick Blues\\" video in 1965? ","correct":"Allen Ginsburg","answerA":"Allen Ginsburg","answerB":"Jack Kerouac","answerC":"Gregory Corso","answerD":"Lawrence Ferlinghetti","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- The Cherry Poppin\' Daddies released this song in 1997 the title of which refers to a series of confrontations in 1943 in LA where Mexican Youth were attacked by US soldiers.","correct":"The Zoot Suit Riots","answerA":"The Zoot Suit Riots","answerB":"The Brown Shirts Riots","answerC":"The West Coast War Riots","answerD":"The Boot Suit Riots","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- In 2000 this female rock singer from Ohio was arrested along with other People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals activists at a Gap store for slashing leather products.","correct":"Chrissie Hynde","answerA":"Chrissie Hynde","answerB":"Natalie Merchant","answerC":"Alison Moyet","answerD":"Tracy Chapman","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- This 1970\'s, New York based, art rock band is said to have inspired the democratic revolution in Czechoslovakia in 1989.","correct":"The Velvet Underground","answerA":"The Velvet Underground","answerB":"Sonic Youth","answerC":"Kraftwerk","answerD":"Devo","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- The spoken word album An American Prayer by Jim Morrison and the Doors was nominated for a Grammy in what year?","correct":"1978","answerA":"1978","answerB":"1956","answerC":"1983","answerD":"1999","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- This 1990 song by X Clan recalls a New York City-wide protest against police brutality on 1989 when demonstrators took over the Brooklyn Bridge. What was the title of the song?","correct":"\\"A Day of Outrage, Operation Snatchback\\"","answerA":"\\"A Day of Outrage, Operation Snatchback\\"","answerB":"\\"Days of Rage, Operation Take it Back\\"","answerC":"\\"Chaos Days- Operation Stand Up for Justice\\"","answerD":"\\"A Day of Confrontation- Operation Take it to the Bridge\\"","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- This  Cameroonian singer was imprisoned in 2008 after criticizing Cameroon president Paul Biya in the song \\"Constitution constip\xe9e.\\" ","correct":"Lapiro de Mbanga","answerA":"Lapiro de Mbanga","answerB":"Emile Kangue","answerC":"Sam Fan Thomas","answerD":"Moni Bile","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- This famous black leftist poet came into prominence in the late 1960\'s with the groundbreaking piece \\"The Revolution Will Not be Televised.\\"","correct":"Gil Scott Heron","answerA":"Gil Scott Heron","answerB":"Abiodun Oyewole","answerC":"Gylan Kain","answerD":"Amiri Baraka","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- What is the subtitle of the 1872 book \\"The Birth of Tragedy\\" by German philosopher Fredrick Nietzsche about the classical German romantic composer Richard Wagner? ","correct":"\\"Through the Spirit of Music\\"","answerA":"\\"Through the Spirit of Music\\"","answerB":"\\"Through War\\"","answerC":"\\"Through Weakness\\"","answerD":"\\"Through the Spirit of Romance\\"","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- The Southern California band Sublime released the song \\"April 29, 1992 (Miami)\\" in 1996. What was the song about?","correct":"The LA Uprising against police brutality","answerA":"The LA Uprising against police brutality","answerB":"The 1968 police riot at the Democratic National Convention in Chicago","answerC":"Looting in Miami after Hurricane Janice","answerD":"Unrest in Miami after a security guard shot an 11 year old in the back","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- Calypso singer Harry Belafonte was arrested outside of this embassy in 1985 protesting Apartited.","correct":"South African","answerA":"South African","answerB":"Egypt","answerC":"Chad","answerD":"Nigeria","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- This singer who has been called \\"the voice of Egypt\\" released the song \\"#Jan25\\"- a 2011 record about the revolutionary movement that ousted Hosni Mubarak and the role that Twitter played in spreading the revolution. ","correct":"Mohamed Mounir","answerA":"Mohamed Mounir","answerB":"Amr Diab","answerC":"Hany Shaker","answerD":"Tamer Hosny","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- Who said this \\"For art to be \\"unpolitical\\" means only to ally itself with the \'ruling\' group.\'\\" ","correct":"Playwrite and Artist Bertolt Brecht","answerA":"Playwrite and Artist Bertolt Brecht","answerB":"Musician and Activist Penny Rimbaud","answerC":"Poet and Essayist Antonin Artaud","answerD":"Composer Kurt Weill","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- The Public Enemy song \\"Black Steel in the Hour of Chaos\\" off the 1988 album It Takes a Nation of Millions to Hold us Back, was a fictional account of what?","correct":"A prison uprising","answerA":"A prison uprising","answerB":"A race war","answerC":"A street protest","answerD":"A street battle during war time","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- This Agit Prop punk feminist group from Russia was arrested in March 2012 after performing an anti-Putin \\"punk prayer\\" inside Moscow\'s Cathedral of Christ the Saviour","correct":"Pussy Riot","answerA":"Pussy Riot","answerB":"The Living Theater","answerC":"Agit-prop","answerD":"Kraftwerk","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- The song \\"A las Barricadas\\" (\\"To the Barricades\\") written by Valeriano Orob\xf3n Fern\xe1ndez in 1936, was a popular revolutionary song with anarchists during what conflict?","correct":"The Spanish Civil War","answerA":"The Spanish Civil War","answerB":"World War II","answerC":"World War I","answerD":"The Spanish American War","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- The Ronnie Dyson song \\"Aquarius\\" a late 1960\'s anthem for the counterculture, appeared in what famous musical?","correct":"Hair","answerA":"Hair","answerB":"West Side Story","answerC":"Jesus Christ Superstar","answerD":"Rent","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- The female folk singer  Madeline Davis wrote this song after attending her first gay and lesbian rights march for civil rights in 1971.","correct":"\\"Stonewall Nation\\"","answerA":"\\"Stonewall Nation\\"","answerB":"\\"Outta the Closet\\"","answerC":"\\"Out and Proud\\"","answerD":"\\"Rainbow Pride\\"","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- Singer/ songwriter Jackson Browne got arrested protesting nuclear power at what power plant in 1981?","correct":"Diablo Canyon","answerA":"Diablo Canyon","answerB":"Grand Canyon","answerC":"King\'s Canyon","answerD":"Copper Canyon","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- The BBC designated this Bob Marley and the Wailers song as \\"Song of the Millennium.\\" ","correct":"\\"One Love\\"","answerA":"\\"One Love\\"","answerB":"\\"Redemption Song\\"","answerC":"\\"Get Up Stand Up\\"","answerD":"\\"Exodus\\" ","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- In the 1961 song \\"America\\" from the musical West Side Story the boys say \\"Life is all right in America\\" and the girls reply?","correct":"\\"If you\'re all white in America\\"","answerA":"\\"If you\'re all white in America\\"","answerB":"\\"If you are white in America\\"","answerC":"\\"If you act right in America\\"","answerD":"\\"If you have might in America\\"","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- The shock metal band GWAR released their second album America Must be Destroyed in what year?","correct":"1992","answerA":"1992","answerB":"1986","answerC":"1998","answerD":"2001","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- This member of the Clash got arrested in 2011 with Greenpeace members for storming the Leiv Eriksson oil rig near Greenland in a speedboat to protest off shore oil drilling.","correct":"Paul Simonon","answerA":"Paul Simonon","answerB":"Mick Jones","answerC":"Joe Strummer","answerD":"Keith Levene","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- This Irish singer wrote \\"The Foggy Dew\\" a 1919 song  about the Easter Rising- a five day armed insurrection against the British in 1916. ","correct":"Canon O\'Neill","answerA":"Canon O\'Neill","answerB":"Derek Warfield","answerC":"David Kincaid","answerD":"The Clancy Brothers And Tommy Makem","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- The civil rights literary legend Maya Angelou teamed up with what famous soul music duo to record the 1996 album Been Found?","correct":"Ashford and Simpson","answerA":"Ashford and Simpson","answerB":"Peaches and Herb","answerC":"Hall and Oats","answerD":"Sam and Dave","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- The opening performance of this modern ballet piece by composer Igor Stravinsky in 1913 led to a riot.","correct":"Rite of Spring","answerA":"Rite of Spring","answerB":"The Death of Summer","answerC":"The Shovel","answerD":"My Dada Night Dream","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- Denise Ho, a Canto- pop singer, was arrested by Chinese authorities in 2014 protesting what?","correct":"The use of tear gas on protesters opposing its policies in Hong Kong","answerA":"The use of tear gas on protesters opposing its policies in Hong Kong","answerB":"The use of live rounds on workers protesting its labor policies.","answerC":"The invasion of Zambia by the military Chinese in 2009","answerD":"The bombing of a Peruvian airliner by the Chinese air force in 2011","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- The song \\"La Marseillaise,\\" the main anthem of the French Revolution created by Claude Joseph Rouget de Lisle was banned by which king and dictator?","correct":"Louis the XVIII and Napoleon the III","answerA":"Louis the XVIII and Napoleon the III","answerB":"King James the VIII and Julius Caesar","answerC":"King Louis the LXV and Napoleon the III","answerD":"Louis the XIV and Napoleon Bonaparte","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- What was the first recorded account of a musician destroying his instrument on stage?","correct":"Rockin\' Rocky Rockwell in 1956","answerA":"Rockin\' Rocky Rockwell in 1957","answerB":"Kurt Cobain of Nirvana in 1991","answerC":"Pete Townsend of the Who in 1966","answerD":"Keith Moon of the Who in 1966","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- The song \\"Revolution\\" by the British shoegaze band Spacemen 3 was released in what year?","correct":"1988","answerA":"1988","answerB":"1991","answerC":"2003","answerD":"1979","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- These two Tibetan musicians started serving four year sentences in 2012 after releasing the album The Pain of an Unhealed Wound- a protest album around the Chinese occupation.","correct":"Pema Trinley and Chakdor","answerA":"Pema Trinley and Chakdor","answerB":"Yungchen Lhamo and Karjam Saeji","answerC":"Danny Becher and Techung","answerD":"Choying Drolma & Steve Tibbetts","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION ROUND- \\"Hasta Siempre,Commandante\\" (\\"Until Forever, Commander\\") is a 1965 song based on Che Guevara\'s farewell address in Cuba before he went to the Congo and Bolivia to join the revolutionary efforts in those counties. Who wrote the song?","correct":"Cuban singer Carlos Puebla","answerA":"Cuban singer Carlos Puebla","answerB":"Cuban singer Benny Mor\xe9","answerC":"Cuban singer Ra\xfal Planas","answerD":"Chilean composer Sergio Ortega","round":"revRound"},{"question":"","correct":"","answerA":"","answerB":"","answerC":"","answerD":"","round":""},{"question":"RAD ROUND- What\'s the name of Gil Scott Heron\'s famous spoken word performance piece about Watergate released in 1974?","correct":"H2O Gate Blues","answerA":"H2O Gate Blues","answerB":"Saturday Night Massacre","answerC":"The Ag-new Blues","answerD":"The Four Asses of the Apocalypse","round":"radRound"},{"question":"REBELLION ROUND- The arrest of members of this hip-hop act in 1989 for performing an anti-police song during a show in Detroit led to a concert riot.","correct":"NWA","answerA":"NWA","answerB":"A Tribe Called Quest","answerC":"Public Enemy","answerD":"Run DMC","round":"rebelRound"},{"question":"RESISTANCE ROUND- This British born rapper was arrested and deported by ICE officials while in Atlanta in 2019. He later donated 25,000 to the Southern Poverty Law Center to fight against ICE abuses.","correct":"21 Savage","answerA":"22 Savage","answerB":"J. Cole","answerC":"Sole","answerD":"Lil\' Wayne","round":"resRound"},{"question":"REVOLUTION  ROUND- Who wrote the 1871 socialist anthem the \\"International.\\" ","correct":"Anarchist, Eugene Pottier","answerA":"Anarchist, Eugene Pottier","answerB":"Communist, Karl Marx","answerC":"Social Democrat, Kurt Weill","answerD":"John Reed, Socialist","round":"revRound"}]')},47:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Australia banned this song by the Kinks in 1970 due to its transgender theme.","correct":"\\"Lola\\"","answerA":"\\"Lola\\"","answerB":"\\"All Day and All of the Night\\"","answerC":"\\"Androgynous\\"","answerD":"\\"Celluloid Heroes\\""},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Lena Horne, a New York based jazz and soul singer was blacklisted from performing in the US during the 1950\'s due to what?","correct":"Having communist affiliations","answerA":"Having communist affiliations","answerB":"Dating a white man","answerC":"Speaking out against","answerD":"Being addicted to pain pills"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Taylor Swift broke her political silence in 2018 and endorsed which Democratic candidate for US Senate in Tennessee?","correct":"Phil Bredesen","answerA":"Phil Bredesen","answerB":"Al Gore","answerC":"Lamar Alexander","answerD":"Bill Lee"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Which punk legend has refused to sign on to an Israeli musician boycott labelling the effort \\"left-wing bullshit.\\"","correct":"Johnny Lydon (AKA Johnny","answerA":"Johnny Lydon (AKA Johnny","answerB":"Johnny Ramone","answerC":"Stiv Bators","answerD":"Kurt Cobain"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- The E Street Band guitarist Little Steven once declared that he \\"wasn\'t gonna play\\" what South African venue due to its apartheid policies in South Africa. ","correct":"Sun City","answerA":"Sun City","answerB":"Thornybush Game Lodge","answerC":"Swadini","answerD":"Mount Amanzi"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- What is the name of the Alabama concert hall that Ray Charles refused to perform at in 1961 due to its policy on racial segregation?","correct":"Bell Auditorium","answerA":"Bell Auditorium","answerB":"Mark C. Smith Concert Hall","answerC":"Alabama Gulf Coast Music Hall","answerD":"Druid City Music Hall"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- The Gang of Four song \\"I Love a Man in a Uniform\\" was banned by the BBC during what war? ","correct":"Falkland Islands War","answerA":"Falkland Islands War","answerB":"The India Pakistan Conflict","answerC":"The first Iraq war in 1991","answerD":"The Vietnam War"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Joe Pesci and Frank Sinatra threatened violence against this artist for her views on Pope John Paul the II and her refusal to sing the Star Spangled Banner before a show.","correct":"Sinead O\'Conner","answerA":"Sinead O\'Conner","answerB":"Joan Biaz","answerC":"Yoko Ono","answerD":"Madonna"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- This all black hardcore punk band was banned in from many venues in  their home town of Washington D.C. because of their raucous shows.","correct":"Bad Brains","answerA":"Bad Brains","answerB":"Living Color","answerC":"Fishbone","answerD":"Death"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- The Dead Kennedys were charged with distribution of harmful matter to minors because of a poster that was included in their 1984 Frankenchrist album. Which artist created it?","correct":"HR Giger","answerA":"HR Giger","answerB":"Salvador Dali","answerC":"Keith Hering","answerD":"Peter Max"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Why was Mike Muir of Suicidal Tendencies detained by the U.S. Secret Service in 1984?","correct":"For  singing the line \\"I Shot Reagan!\\" in a song","answerA":"For  singing the line \\"I Shot Reagan!\\" in a song","answerB":"He was suspected of being a drug runner for a California gang","answerC":"He failed to pay taxes in 1978 and in 1981","answerD":"He had three felony warrants out for his arrest"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Kayne West was booed on Saturday Night Live in 2018 for his support of what politician?","correct":"Donald Trump","answerA":"Donald Trump","answerB":"Barack Obama","answerC":"Ronald Reagan","answerD":"Sarah Palin"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- This all female, country trio lost much of their fan base after speaking out against George W Bush and the Iraq war at a London concert in 2003.","correct":"The Dixie Chicks","answerA":"The Dixie Chicks","answerB":"SHeDaisy","answerC":"Lady Antebellum","answerD":"The Band Perry"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- When asked by a CNN host whether she supported the Gulf War in 2003 this pop artist said \\"Honestly, I think we should just trust our president in every decision that he makes...\\"","correct":"Brittany Spears","answerA":"Brittany Spears","answerB":"Paula Abdul","answerC":"Taylor Swift","answerD":"Christina Aguilera"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- This 1975 song by county music star Loretta Lynn was banned by radio stations across the U.S. when it was released.","correct":"\\"The Pill\\"","answerA":"\\"The Pill\\"","answerB":"\\"Another Man Loved Me Last Night\\"","answerC":"\\"Not Gonna Take Your Beatin\'\\"","answerD":"\\"Beautiful Unhappy Home\\""},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Who was the first rock musician to be arrest while on stage?","correct":"Jim Morrison","answerA":"Jim Morrison","answerB":"Bill Haley","answerC":"Jimi Hendricks","answerD":"Elvis Presley"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Christian fundamentalists organized record burning protests in 1966 after this rock icon claimed that his band was more popular than Jesus.","correct":"John Lennon","answerA":"John Lennon","answerB":"Brian Love","answerC":"Frank Zappa","answerD":"Mick Jagger"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Which anti-fascist song by the Sex Pistols was both banned and a number one \\"hit\\" on the U.K. record charts in 1977? ","correct":"\\"God Save the Queen\\"","answerA":"\\"God Save the Queen\\"","answerB":"\\"No One is Innocent\\"","answerC":"\\"Holiday in the Sun\\"","answerD":"\\"Bloody Revolutions\\""},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- The BBC banned this song in 1968 from the Beatles due to its alleged sexual connotations.","correct":"\\"Happiness is a Warm Gun\\"","answerA":"\\"Happiness is a Warm Gun\\"","answerB":"\\"I Am the Walrus\\"","answerC":"\\"Because\\"","answerD":"\\"Why Don\'t We Do it in the Road\\""},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- In 2012, this artist said, \\"I don\'t talk about politics because it might influence other people. I don\'t know enough yet in life to be telling people who to vote for.\\"","correct":"Taylor Swift","answerA":"Taylor Swift","answerB":"Selena Gomez","answerC":"Demi Lovato","answerD":"Miley Cyrus"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- After several venues cancelled tour dates in 2018, Fat Mike, lead singer of the punk band NOFX, was forced to apologize for mocking the victims of what tragedy?","correct":"The 2017 mass shooting at Harvest Country Music Festival in Las Vegas","answerA":"The 2017 mass shooting at Harvest Country Music Festival in Las Vegas","answerB":"The Sandy Hook mass school shooting in Connecticut","answerC":"The victims of the Virgina Tech massacre","answerD":"The Manchester mass shooting at an Ariana Grande concert"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- This San Francisco based rock band was fined $1,000 for onstage profanity in Oklahoma City back in 1970.","correct":"Jefferson Airplane","answerA":"Jefferson Airplane","answerB":"The Steve Miller Band","answerC":"The Grateful Dead","answerD":"The Tubes"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Walmart refused to carry this artist\'s second album because of a song that condemned the chain store for selling the type of guns involved in mass shootings.","correct":"Sheryl Crow","answerA":"Sheryl Crow","answerB":"Ariana Grande","answerC":"Madonna","answerD":"Ani DiFranco"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- In the summer of 2011, Punks Against Apartheid came together to convince this punk artist not to play a concert in Tel Aviv.","correct":"Jello Biafra","answerA":"Jello Biafra","answerB":"Richard Hell","answerC":"Johnny Lydon","answerD":"Henry Rollins"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- What police officers association refused to join a boycott of Ice T and Time Warner in 1992 in response to the release of the song \\"Cop Killer\\" by the band Body Count? ","correct":"The National Black Police Officers Association","answerA":"The National Black Police Officers Association","answerB":"National Association of Police Organizations","answerC":"The All American Peace Officers Alliance","answerD":"The National Peace Officers Association"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- This clarinetist and bandleader was blacklisted and brought before the House on Un-American Activities for having attended Communist meetings in 1950\'s.","correct":"Artie Shaw","answerA":"Artie Shaw","answerB":"Woody Allen","answerC":"Benny Goodman","answerD":"Tommy Dorsey"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Walmart and K-Mart wouldn\'t stock the 1994 Nirvana album \\"In Utero\\" because of what song?","correct":"\\"Rape Me\\"","answerA":"\\"Rape Me\\"","answerB":"\\"I Hate Myself and Want to Die\\"","answerC":"\\"Serve the Servants\\"","answerD":"\\"Pennyroyal Tea\\""},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- This rap group called for a boycott of Arizona in the early 1990\'s for its refusal to recognize Martin Luther King Jr\'s. birthday as an official holiday.","correct":"Public Enemy","answerA":"Public Enemy","answerB":"Poor Righteous Teachers","answerC":"Stetsasonic","answerD":"Black Sheep"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Stevie Wonder has boycotted Florida since 2010 after Robert Zimmerman gunned down, and was acquitted of murdering, this unarmed black teen.","correct":"Trayvon Martin","answerA":"Trayvon Martin","answerB":"Michael Brown","answerC":"Breona Taylor","answerD":"Stephon Clark"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- The organizers of Woodstock in 1969 decided not to invite this band due to the lead singer\'s recent arrest in Miami on indecent exposure.","correct":"The Doors","answerA":"The Doors","answerB":"The Rolling Stones","answerC":"The Beatles","answerD":"Pink Floyd"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Sinead O\'Conner was booed on stage at a Bob Dylan tribute concert a couple weeks after she did what on Saturday Night Live in 1992?","correct":"Rip up a picture of the Pope","answerA":"Rip up a picture of the Pope","answerB":"Rip up a picture of John Major","answerC":"Rip up a picture of George Bush","answerD":"Rip up a picture of Dennis Miller"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- In 2010 this all Black, female singing group released the song \\"Are We A Nation?\\" in response to SB 1070, an anti-immigration law passed by Arizona.","correct":"Sweet Honey in the Rock","answerA":"Sweet Honey in the Rock","answerB":"Destiny\'s Child","answerC":"En Vogue","answerD":"TLC"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Rihanna refused the NFL\'s offer to play the halftime super bowl show in 2019 to show solidarity with which athlete?","correct":"Colin Kaepernic","answerA":"Colin Kaepernic","answerB":"Eric Reid","answerC":"Reggie Williams","answerD":"Tom Brady"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- In 1972 David Bowie came out as bisexual in an interview with what music magazine?","correct":"Melody Maker","answerA":"Melody Maker","answerB":"Circus Magazine","answerC":"Sounds","answerD":"Rolling Stone"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Elvis Costello has refused to play in this country due to their treatment of residents of the Gaza Strip.","correct":"Israel","answerA":"Israel","answerB":"Egypt","answerC":"Iraq","answerD":"Turkey"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- In 1999 the National Fraternal Order of Police called for a boycott of Rage Against the Machine and the Beastie Boys for their support of what political prisoner?","correct":"Mumia Abu Jamal","answerA":"Mumia Abu Jamal","answerB":"Geronimo Pratt","answerC":"Marilyn Buck","answerD":"David Gilbert"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- Police organizations across the U.S. called for a boycott of this group for their 1988 song \\"Fuck tha Police.\\"","correct":"NWA","answerA":"NWA","answerB":"Public Enemy","answerC":"X- Clan","answerD":"EPMD"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- In 2015 the band Wilco decided to boycott this state due to its passage of the Religious Freedom Restoration Act, a law that legalizes discrimination against LGBTQI residents.","correct":"Arizona","answerA":"Arizona","answerB":"Maine","answerC":"Texas","answerD":"Iowa"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- The University of Minnesota banned this artist in 1952 for his communist political beliefs.","correct":"Paul Robeson","answerA":"Paul Robeson","answerB":"Harry Belafonte","answerC":"John Coltrane","answerD":"Louis Armstrong"},{"question":"SHUT UP AND SING- The Miami Fraternal Order of Police called for a boycott of this artist following her Super Bowl performance in which she led dancers dressed like Black Panthers in a halftime performance of the song \\"Formation.\\"","correct":"Beyonc\xe9","answerA":"Beyonc\xe9","answerB":"Azealia Banks","answerC":"Lorde","answerD":"Nicki Minaj"}]')},48:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"field1":"Question 1","question":"In the human rights anthem \\"Get up, Stand up\\" Bob Marley is joined by who on lead vocals?","correct":"Peter Tosh","answerA":"Peter Tosh","answerB":"Joe Higgs","answerC":"Jimmy Cliff","answerD":"Desmond Dekker","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 2","question":"Green Day recorded a cover of this John Lennon song in 2007 for an Amnesty International benefit for Darfur.","correct":"\\"Working Class Hero\\"","answerA":"\\"Working Class Hero\\"","answerB":"\\"Imagine\\"","answerC":"\\"Give Peace a Chance\\"","answerD":"\\"Cold Turkey\\"","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 3","question":"What was the Bruce Springsteen song \\"Born in the USA\\" about?","correct":"The struggles of working class, Vietnam War veterans returning back the US","answerA":"The struggles of working class, Vietnam War veterans returning back the US","answerB":"Supporting a strong military","answerC":"Being proud to be an American","answerD":"Supporting Ronald Reagan","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 4","question":"From which Bob Dylan song did the radical 1970\'s leftist group The Weathermen take their name?","correct":"\\"Subterranean Homesick Blues\\"","answerA":"\\"Subterranean Homesick Blues\\"","answerB":"\\"Everybody Must Get Stoned\\"","answerC":"\\"Tears in Heaven\\"","answerD":"\\"Like a Rolling Stone\\"","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 5*","question":"What\'s the first line in Patti Smith\'s classic remake of the song \\"Gloria\\" in 1975?","correct":"\\"Jesus died for somebody\'s sins but not mine\\"","answerA":"\\"Jesus died for somebody\'s sins but not mine\\"","answerB":"\\"Like to tell you about my baby\\"","answerC":"\\"Gloria, your always on the run now\\"","answerD":"\\"Gloria you\'re the one for me\\"","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 6*","question":"Rolling Stone magazine voted this Clash record the best studio album  of the 1980\'s.","correct":"London Calling","answerA":"London Calling","answerB":"The Clash","answerC":"Cut the Crap","answerD":"Combat Rock","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 7*","question":"The protest song \\"Mississippi Goddamn\\" was written by Nina Simone in response to what two incidents? ","correct":"The assassination of NAACP leader Medgar Evers, and the bombing of the 16th Street Baptist Church in Birmingham, Alabama, which killed four black girls.","answerA":"The assassination of NAACP leader Medgar Evers, and the bombing of the 16th Street Baptist Church in Birmingham, Alabama, which killed four black girls.","answerB":"The US invasion of Cambodia, and the assassination of MLK","answerC":"The killing of Malcolm X and JFK","answerD":"The Jackson State Killings of two students by the Mississippi State Police and the US bombing of Laos","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 8*","question":"What album did the song Pride (in the name of love) a tribute to Martin Luther King Jr. by U2 appear on?","correct":"Unforgettable Fire","answerA":"Unforgettable Fire","answerB":"Boy","answerC":"October","answerD":"Rattle and Hum","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 9*","question":"Did Joan Biaz perform at the historic Civil Rights March on Washington in August of 1963?","correct":"Yes","answerA":"Yes","answerB":"No","answerC":"","answerD":"","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 10*","question":"The hip-hop group Public Enemy released their influential, landmark album It Takes a Nation of Millions to Hold Us Back in what year?","correct":"1988","answerA":"1988","answerB":"1990","answerC":"1993","answerD":"1986","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 11*","question":"1997 this band won a Grammy for best metal performance.","correct":"Rage Against the Machine","answerA":"Rage Against the Machine","answerB":"System of a Down","answerC":"Metallica","answerD":"Jethro Tull","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 12*","question":"In what year was Yoko Ono born?","correct":"1933","answerA":"1933","answerB":"1945","answerC":"1923","answerD":"1959","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 13*","question":"The 1979 song \\"At Home He\'s a Tourist\\" by the post punk group Gang of Four was banned by which network?","correct":"BBC","answerA":"BBC","answerB":"ABC","answerC":"NBC","answerD":"CBS","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 14*","question":"What term best describes Sinead O\'Conner\'s Political views","correct":"Pacifist","answerA":"Pacifist","answerB":"Anarchist","answerC":"Nationalist","answerD":"Republican","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 15*","question":"The Dead Kennedys\' punk classic \\"Holiday in Cambodia\\" a song that mocked liberal yuppie hypocrisy, came out in what year?","correct":"1979","answerA":"1980","answerB":"1973","answerC":"1983","answerD":"1979","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 16*","question":"Who said this? \\"Religion is finely designed to divide and separate; spirituality brings unity and forgiveness and compassion.\\" ","correct":"Carlos Santana","answerA":"Carlos Santana","answerB":"Ram Dass","answerC":"Dalai Lama","answerD":"Ravi Shankar","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 17*","question":"What was the first single released by the Sex Pistols in November of 1976?","correct":"\\"Anarchy in the UK\\"","answerA":"\\"Anarchy in the UK\\"","answerB":"\\"God Save the Queen\\"","answerC":"\\"Bodies\\"","answerD":"\\"Pretty Vacant\\"","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 18*","question":"Which female hip-hop artist founded The Refugee Project in 1996 -a charity organization for at risk youth?","correct":"Lauryn Hill","answerA":"Lauryn Hill","answerB":"Lil\' Kim","answerC":"Foxy Brown","answerD":"Monie Love","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 19*","question":"At the beginning of the Bikini Kill song \\"Double Dare Ya\\" what does lead singer Kathleen Hanna call for? ","correct":"\\"Revolution!\\"","answerA":"\\"Revolution!\\"","answerB":"\\"Peace\\"","answerC":"\\"Love\\"","answerD":"\\"Resistance!\\"","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 20*","question":"What incident inspired the Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young song \\"Ohio\\"?","correct":"The shooting of four anti-war student protesters by National Guard troops at Kent State in 1970.","answerA":"The shooting of four anti-war student protesters by National Guard troops at Kent State in 1970.","answerB":"The shooting of John Lennon","answerC":"A student riot in Youngstown in 1970","answerD":"The death of Mary Rose Oakar","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 21*","question":"The song \\"Smalltown Boy,\\" from the 1980\'s UK synth-pop band, Bronski Beat, was about what?","correct":"A young man leaving his hometown because he\'s gay","answerA":"A young man leaving his hometown because he\'s gay","answerB":"A boy being forced into a mental institution because he\'s gay","answerC":"A black man being chased out of his hometown because he dated a white girl","answerD":"A boy being thrown out of his house for being gay","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 22*","question":"The Song \\"Let There be Peace\\" was released in 2013 on what Sweet Honey and the Rock record?","correct":"A Tribute - Live! Jazz at Lincoln Center","answerA":"Live from Carnegie Hall","answerB":"Live Jazz from the Kennedy Center!","answerC":"A Tribute - Live! Jazz at Lincoln Center","answerD":"Live from the 9:30 Club!","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 23*","question":"This deep throated, U.S. based baritone was investigated and blacklisted during the late 1940\'s and 1950\'s for supporting civil rights and pro-Soviet policies.","correct":"Paul Robeson","answerA":"Paul Robeson","answerB":"Harry Belafonte","answerC":"Louis Armstrong","answerD":"Ossie Davis","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 24*","question":"The 1944 Woody Guthrie song \\"This Land is Your Land\\" was written in reaction to what nationalist song?","correct":"\\"God Bless America\\"  ","answerA":"\\"God Bless America\\"  ","answerB":"\\"the Star Spangled Banner\\"","answerC":"\\"America the Beautiful\\"","answerD":"\\"God Bless the USA\\"","Further Expl.":""},{"field1":"Question 25*","question":"In the 1976 song \\"Rat Race\\" off the album Rastaman Vibration, Bob Marley sings that \\"Rasta don\'t work for no\\" Who?","correct":"CIA","answerA":"FBI","answerB":"UN","answerC":"ICE","answerD":"CIA","Further Expl.":""}]')},56:function(e,n,a){},57:function(e,n,a){},68:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse("{}")},69:function(e,n,a){"use strict";a.r(n);var r=a(2),t=a(3),o=a.n(t),s=a(33),i=a.n(s),c=(a(56),a(57),a(16)),h=a(10),l=(a(37),a(38),a(19)),u=a(20),d=a(22),w=a(21),m=(a(49).a.initializeApp({apiKey:"AIzaSyDg-tOKM0bDYI5JkPWsv_CpkpkVE7p3PkU",authDomain:"rrtrivia.firebaseapp.com",projectId:"rrtrivia",storageBucket:"rrtrivia.appspot.com",messagingSenderId:"83676546949",appId:"1:83676546949:web:c94a5cfe7c8b1443e226ec",measurementId:"G-NETL2F0MJ1"}),function(e){Object(d.a)(a,e);var n=Object(w.a)(a);function a(e){return Object(l.a)(this,a),n.call(this,e)}return Object(u.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(r.jsx)("div",{})}}]),a}(o.a.Component)),g=a(23),p=a(7),f=a(8);function b(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    text-align: center;\n   \n    /* border-radius: 5px; */\n    /* padding: 10px; */\n    font-size: 25px;\n    font-weight: 500;\n  \n    /* background-color: #e1e3e2; */\n    color: #292e29;\n"]);return b=function(){return e},e}var B=f.a.div(b());function C(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    text-align: center;\n    background-color: white;\n    border-radius: 2px;\n    font-size: 25px;\n    border-style: solid;\n    border-color: black;\n    border-width: 2px;\n    width: 100%;\n    padding:14px;\n\n"]);return C=function(){return e},e}var y=f.a.button(C());function A(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    display: grid;\n    gap: 30px;\n    grid-template-columns: 1fr ;\n    margin: auto;\n\n\n    \n"]);return A=function(){return e},e}var R=f.a.div(A());function S(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n\nfont-family: 'Ariel', sans-serif;\nfont-weight: 900;\nfont-size: 50px;\ncolor: white;\ntext-align: center;\n"]);return S=function(){return e},e}var D=f.a.h1(S());function E(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    display: block;\n    background-color: white;\n    width: 70%;\n    box-shadow: 5px 10px 8px #888888;\n    margin: auto;\n    padding: 30px;\n    margin-top:80px;\n"]);return E=function(){return e},e}var T=f.a.div(E());function M(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    display: grid;\n    grid-gap: 30px;\n\n    margin: auto;\n\n    \n"]);return M=function(){return e},e}var v=f.a.div(M());function k(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    display: grid;\n    grid-gap: 30px;\n    /* background-color: #c1dec4; */\n    padding:20px;\n    margin: auto;\n    width: 70%;\n    box-shadow: 5px 10px 8px #888888;\n    margin-top: 80px;\n\n    \n"]);return k=function(){return e},e}var I=f.a.div(k());function L(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    display: block;\n    background-color: black;\n    text-align: center;\n    width: 80%;\n    box-shadow: 5px 10px 8px #888888;\n    margin: auto;\n    padding: 30px;\n    margin-top:100px;\n    border-radius: 5px;\n"]);return L=function(){return e},e}var P=f.a.div(L());function N(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    text-align: left;\n    \n    font-size: 20px;\n    font-weight: 600;\n\n    margin-top: 10px;\n    border-radius: 3px;\n    color: indigo;\n\n"]);return N=function(){return e},e}var U=f.a.div(N());function O(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    margin-left:20px;\n    margin-top:20px;\n    text-align: left;\n    background-color: lightgray;\n    font-size: 25px;\n    font-weight: 500;\n    width: 120px;\n    padding:20px;\n    border-radius: 3px;\n\n"]);return O=function(){return e},e}var q=f.a.div(O());function j(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    background-color: black ;\n    border: solid;\n    font-size: 20px;\n    padding:15px;\n    /* width: 100px; */\n    color: #F37188;\n    border-radius: 5px;\n"]);return j=function(){return e},e}var x=f.a.button(j());function W(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    text-align: right;\n    margin-right: 70px;\n    margin-top: 0px;\n    font-size: 40px;\n    font-weight: 600;\n\n    margin-top: 10px;\n    border-radius: 3px;\n    color: indigo;\n\n"]);return W=function(){return e},e}var H=f.a.div(W()),G=a(28),F=a.n(G),J=function(e){Object(d.a)(a,e);var n=Object(w.a)(a);function a(e){var r;return Object(l.a)(this,a),(r=n.call(this,e)).isCorrect=r.isCorrect.bind(Object(g.a)(r)),r.advanceRound=r.advanceRound.bind(Object(g.a)(r)),r.getQuestionsForRound=r.getQuestionsForRound.bind(Object(g.a)(r)),r.state={questions:[],currentQuestion:0,correct:null,score:0,numCorrect:0,numQuestions:0,isTimeUp:!1,round:"basic",roundString:"",time:24e4},r}return Object(u.a)(a,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){for(var e=this.props.data,n=0;n<e.length;n++){var a=Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length),r=e[n];e[n]=e[a],e[a]=r}this.setState({questions:e})}},{key:"advanceRound",value:function(){"basic"===this.state.round?this.setState({round:"radRound",questions:[],currentQuestion:0,roundString:"Radical Round",isTimeUp:!1,correct:null}):"radRound"===this.state.round?this.setState({round:"rebelRound",questions:[],roundString:"Rebellion Round",currentQuestion:0,isTimeUp:!1,correct:null}):"rebelRound"===this.state.round?this.setState({round:"resRound",questions:[],roundString:"Resistance Round",currentQuestion:0,isTimeUp:!1,correct:null}):"resRound"===this.state.round&&this.setState({round:"revRound",roundString:"Revolution Round",questions:[],currentQuestion:0,isTimeUp:!1,correct:null})}},{key:"getQuestionsForRound",value:function(){for(var e=[],n=this.props.advanced,a=0;a<n.length;a++)n[a].round===this.state.round&&e.push(n[a]);for(var r=0;r<e.length;r++){var t=Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length),o=e[r];e[r]=e[t],e[t]=o}this.setState({questions:e})}},{key:"isCorrect",value:function(e,n){var a=this;console.log(n),"basic"===this.state.round?e===n?(this.setState({correct:!0}),setTimeout((function(){a.setState({correct:null,currentQuestion:a.state.currentQuestion+1,numCorrect:a.state.numCorrect+1,numQuestions:a.state.numQuestions+1,score:a.state.score+100})}),2e3)):(this.setState({correct:!1}),setTimeout((function(){a.setState({correct:null,currentQuestion:a.state.currentQuestion+1,numQuestions:a.state.numQuestions+1})}),2e3)):e===n?this.setState({correct:!0}):this.setState({correct:!1})}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;if("basic"===this.state.round){function n(){var e=[];e.push(o.answerA),e.push(o.answerB),e.push(o.answerC),e.push(o.answerD);for(var n=0;n<e.length;n++){var a=Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length),r=e[n];e[n]=e[a],e[a]=r}o.answers=e}var a=this.state.questions,t=this.state.currentQuestion,o=a[t];return(t===a.length||this.state.isTimeUp)&&this.state.score<=500?Object(r.jsxs)(P,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(D,{children:"Beginner"}),Object(r.jsxs)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:[" Your final score was ",this.state.score]}),Object(r.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/",children:Object(r.jsx)(x,{children:"Play Again?"})})]}):(t===a.length||this.state.isTimeUp)&&this.state.score>500&&this.state.score<=1e3?Object(r.jsxs)(P,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(D,{children:"Not Bad!"}),Object(r.jsxs)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:[" Your final score was ",this.state.score]}),Object(r.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/",children:Object(r.jsx)(x,{children:"Play Again?"})})]}):(t===a.length||this.state.isTimeUp)&&this.state.score>1e3&&this.state.score<=1400?Object(r.jsxs)(P,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(D,{children:"Good!"}),Object(r.jsxs)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:[" Your final score was ",this.state.score]}),Object(r.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/",children:Object(r.jsx)(x,{children:"Play Again?"})})]}):(t===a.length||this.state.isTimeUp)&&this.state.score>=1500?(setTimeout(this.advanceRound(),5e3),Object(r.jsxs)(P,{children:[Object(r.jsx)("h1",{style:{color:"white",fontSize:"50px"},children:"Excellent!"}),Object(r.jsxs)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:[" Your final score was ",this.state.score,", Welcome to Sudden Death!!"]})]})):a.length>0?(o.answers||n(),console.log(o.answerA),Object(r.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(r.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"inline"},children:[Object(r.jsxs)(q,{children:[this.state.numQuestions,"/",this.state.questions.length,Object(r.jsxs)(U,{children:["Score: ",this.state.score]})]}),Object(r.jsx)(H,{children:Object(r.jsxs)(F.a,{initialTime:this.state.time,direction:"backward",checkpoints:[{time:0,callback:function(){e.setState({isTimeUp:!0})}}],children:[Object(r.jsx)(F.a.Minutes,{}),":",Object(r.jsx)(F.a.Seconds,{})]})})]}),Object(r.jsx)(T,{children:Object(r.jsxs)(v,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(B,{children:o.question}),Object(r.jsx)(R,{children:o.answers.map((function(n){return null===e.state.correct?Object(r.jsx)(y,{onClick:function(){e.isCorrect(o.correct,n)},children:n},Math.random()):!0===e.state.correct?n===o.correct?Object(r.jsx)(y,{style:{backgroundColor:"green",border:"none",color:"white"},children:n},Math.random()):Object(r.jsx)(y,{style:{backgroundColor:"#b3b5b4",border:"none",color:"white"},children:n},Math.random()):!1===e.state.correct?n===o.correct?Object(r.jsx)(y,{style:{backgroundColor:"#07b822",border:"none",color:"white"},children:n},Math.random()):Object(r.jsx)(y,{style:{backgroundColor:"#fc8f8d",border:"none",color:"white"},children:n},Math.random()):void 0}))})]})})]})):Object(r.jsx)("p",{children:" Please Wait ..."})}{function n(){var e=[];e.push(i.answerA),e.push(i.answerB),e.push(i.answerC),e.push(i.answerD);for(var n=0;n<e.length;n++){var a=Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length),r=e[n];e[n]=e[a],e[a]=r}i.answers=e}var s=this.state.questions,i=s[this.state.currentQuestion];return console.log("hello from render",this.state.round),!1===this.state.correct?Object(r.jsxs)(P,{children:[Object(r.jsx)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:" Wrong Answer :("}),Object(r.jsxs)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:[" Your final score was ",this.state.score]}),Object(r.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/",children:Object(r.jsx)(x,{children:"Play Again?"})})]}):!0===this.state.correct&&"revRound"===this.state.round?Object(r.jsxs)(P,{children:[Object(r.jsx)("h1",{style:{color:"white",fontSize:"50px"},children:"Rock On!"}),Object(r.jsx)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:" You answered all of the advanced questions correctly!"}),Object(r.jsxs)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:[" Your final score is ",this.state.score]})]}):!0===this.state.correct?(setTimeout(this.advanceRound(),5e3),Object(r.jsxs)(P,{children:[Object(r.jsx)("h1",{style:{color:"white",fontSize:"50px"},children:"Rock On!"}),Object(r.jsx)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:" You answered right!"}),Object(r.jsxs)("h2",{style:{color:"white"},children:[" Your score is ",this.state.score]})]})):s.length>0?(i.answers||n(),console.log(i.answerA),Object(r.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(r.jsx)("div",{style:{display:"inline"},children:Object(r.jsxs)(q,{children:[this.state.numQuestions,"/",this.state.questions.length,Object(r.jsxs)(U,{children:["Score: ",this.state.score]})]})}),Object(r.jsxs)(I,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(D,{style:{color:"purple",fontWeight:"1200"},children:this.state.roundString}),Object(r.jsx)(B,{children:i.question}),Object(r.jsx)(R,{children:i.answers.map((function(n){return null===e.state.correct?Object(r.jsx)(y,{onClick:function(){e.isCorrect(i.correct,n)},children:n},Math.random()):!0===e.state.correct?n===i.correct?Object(r.jsx)(y,{style:{backgroundColor:"green",border:"none",color:"white"},children:n},Math.random()):Object(r.jsx)(y,{style:{backgroundColor:"#b3b5b4",border:"none",color:"white"},children:n},Math.random()):!1===e.state.correct?n===i.correct?Object(r.jsx)(y,{style:{backgroundColor:"#07b822",border:"none",color:"white"},children:n},Math.random()):Object(r.jsx)(y,{style:{backgroundColor:"#fc8f8d",border:"none",color:"white"},children:n},Math.random()):void 0}))})]})]})):(this.getQuestionsForRound(),Object(r.jsx)("p",{children:" Please Wait ..."}))}}}]),a}(o.a.Component);function z(){var e=Object(p.a)(["\n    background-color: black ;\n    border: solid;\n    font-size: 25px;\n    padding:20px;\n    /* width: 100px; */\n    color: white;\n    border-radius: 5px;\n"]);return z=function(){return e},e}var K=f.a.button(z()),X=function(e){Object(d.a)(a,e);var n=Object(w.a)(a);function a(e){return Object(l.a)(this,a),n.call(this,e)}return Object(u.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"Home",children:Object(r.jsxs)(P,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(D,{children:"Rebel Rock Trivia"}),Object(r.jsx)("h3",{style:{color:"white"},children:" The trivia game where politics and music collide"}),Object(r.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/categories",children:Object(r.jsx)(x,{onClick:function(){console.log("enter")},children:"Enter"})})]})})}}]),a}(o.a.Component),Q=a(50),V=(a(68),a(44)),Y=a(45),Z=a(46),_=a(47),$=a(48);var ee=function(){var e=Object(t.useState)(null),n=Object(Q.a)(e,2),a=n[0],o=n[1];return null===a?Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"Categories",children:Object(r.jsxs)(P,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(D,{children:"Choose a Category "}),Object(r.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"grid",gridGap:"20px",gridTemplateColumns:"1fr 1fr"},children:[Object(r.jsx)(K,{onClick:function(){o(V)},children:" Rebel Rappers "}),Object(r.jsx)(K,{onClick:function(){o(Y)},children:" Rebel Rock Mix "}),Object(r.jsx)(K,{onClick:function(){o($)},children:" Hall of Fame "}),Object(r.jsx)(K,{onClick:function(){o(_)},children:" Shut Up And Sing "})]})]})}):Object(r.jsx)(J,{data:a,advanced:Z})};var ne=function(){return Object(r.jsxs)(c.a,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(h.a,{exact:!0,path:"/",component:X}),Object(r.jsx)(h.a,{exact:!0,path:"/login",component:m}),Object(r.jsx)(h.a,{exact:!0,path:"/quizPage",component:J}),Object(r.jsx)(h.a,{exact:!0,path:"/quizPage/:category",name:"quizPage",render:function(e){console.log(e);var n=e.match.params.category;return console.log(n),Object(r.jsx)("div",{children:Object(r.jsx)(J,{data:!0})})}}),Object(r.jsx)(h.a,{exact:!0,path:"/categories",component:ee})]})},ae=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&a.e(3).then(a.bind(null,70)).then((function(n){var a=n.getCLS,r=n.getFID,t=n.getFCP,o=n.getLCP,s=n.getTTFB;a(e),r(e),t(e),o(e),s(e)}))};i.a.render(Object(r.jsx)(o.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(r.jsx)(ne,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),ae()}},[[69,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.1025d935.chunk.js.map